<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>RIDHWAN</title>
    <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on RIDHWAN</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 21:25:02 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fahimfuad.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>RidDiary 03</title>
      <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/diary/ogranictime/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 21:25:02 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fahimfuad.github.io/diary/ogranictime/</guid>
      <description> Organic Sucks </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MobileUpdate</title>
      <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/mobiletest/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 21:10:50 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/mobiletest/</guid>
      <description>Whhoh, I can now upload posts and diaries from mobile (RIP PC), guess will keep doing that, this is my only source of recreation. I want a add a reaction system badly, but my life is fucked by a lot of things right now ✌️</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RiDepressed</title>
      <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/ridepressed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 22:54:46 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/ridepressed/</guid>
      <description>25 days left till exams, and here I am wasting my time here. Feeling really depressed and sad today, feels like &amp;ldquo;কোথাও chance পামু না&amp;rdquo;, legit this is how I feel right now. I used to be so much confident. It will be a good idea to disassemble my PC, and be a cave man. Yeah, imma disassemble my PC tonight, so this is my last time spending time on this site, I will be back with a post after exams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RidIsAProudISCian</title>
      <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/proudiscians/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 15:47:59 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/proudiscians/</guid>
      <description>Gregorians: Our school provides great education and boasts a prestigious alumni. What does your school have?
ISCians: Bangladeshi Jeffrey Epsteins and alumni&amp;rsquo;s are added bonus.
See, love doesn&amp;rsquo;t see looks &amp;amp; money, it sees pure admiration.
This is their YouTube Channel and they are talking about being sugar daddy here&amp;hellip;
I will buy this book no matter what. Jokes apart, this is a magnificent source of recreaction. I wonder how that girl is with that old man, money?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RidDiary 02</title>
      <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/diary/diary02/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 12:27:37 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fahimfuad.github.io/diary/diary02/</guid>
      <description>Integration done, and I am too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RidIlluminatiThought</title>
      <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/illuminati/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 17:32:52 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/illuminati/</guid>
      <description>If you are a muslim, then you should know the Dajjal, the one eyed satanic form which will come before the doomsday. Just to be clear, I am a practicing muslim and conveying my thoughts and knowledge via this site, this is an unbiased thought on the Illuminati.
Many famous people, Zuck, Elon, Gates, Beyonce, Swift etc. are thought to be a part of the Illuminati. It&amp;rsquo;s basically an organization to control the people of the world in it&amp;rsquo;s way, in a dark way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>রিদ্ হলুদ বিক্রি</title>
      <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/yellowsale/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 21:43:16 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/yellowsale/</guid>
      <description>মা YellowSale এ গেসিল, আমার জন্য জিন্‌স এর প্যান্ট কিনতে&amp;hellip; ছিঁড়া ফাটা প্যান্ট আমি পরি না,মা জানে এইটা।
Sale এ সব ছিঁড়া ফাটা প্যান্ট, মা বলতেসে &amp;ldquo;প্যান্ট কই?&amp;rdquo; লোকজন ছিঁড়া ফাটা প্যান্ট দেখিয়ে বলে এইজে প্যান্ট&amp;hellip;
মাঃ আমার ছেলে ছিঁড়া ফাটা প্যান্ট পড়ে না।
লোকঃ &amp;ldquo;দেখেন গিয়া আপনার ছেলে ছিঁড়া ফাটা প্যান্টই পরবে, এই বয়সের ছেলে ছিঁড়া ফাটা প্যান্টই পরে&amp;rdquo;
মা বাসায় আইসা আমারে জিগায়, তুমি ছিঁড়া ফাটা প্যান্ট পরো?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RidBUPFail</title>
      <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/bupfail/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 01:41:33 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/bupfail/</guid>
      <description>Meh, I expected on waiting list. Am I expecting too much? I mean I studied nothing for BUP, I shouldn&amp;rsquo;t expect a merit. Funny how the 20K fighting for 250 seats, all of my idiot elite homies are rejected too 😂
Bro who is BUP selecting then? Quota idiots? 😂
I know I shouldn&amp;rsquo;t care about BUP, we don&amp;rsquo;t care for BUP, it was more like a tourist exam&amp;hellip;. but it feels sad for some reason even though I didn&amp;rsquo;t prepare for it, getting rejected is tough.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RidDiary 01</title>
      <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/diary/unmath/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 23:00:11 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fahimfuad.github.io/diary/unmath/</guid>
      <description>What&amp;rsquo;s the best time to call your friend? Of course it&amp;rsquo;s 3AM winter night. Get him up from sleep, because I need a fix for my integration.
^ Me at video call 3:05AM</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RidScholarship</title>
      <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/scholarship/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 17:09:10 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/scholarship/</guid>
      <description>Got a dream down today, finally. I lowkey expected talentpool, which started from 1190(approximately), I got 1184 :)
But hey, 048th in general is not bad, 1st from Joseph EV ✌️, 3rd from Whole Joseph
AND
162th in Dhaka Board!
Man it feels so good to fulfill promises, I promised my queen of this, made it and she was like &amp;ldquo;পাইস তাইলে, ভালোই&amp;rdquo;, this is not a complement, got none but hey, I know She is really happy inside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RidBUPDrill</title>
      <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/bupdrill/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 00:10:50 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/bupdrill/</guid>
      <description>BUP was a nice experience, cantonment is nice, the environment was nice. Question standard was pretty okay even though I was not able to unleash my full potential there, 250 seats for 20K in FST, pretty hard. My brain was vibing on One Kiss by Dua Lipa during the exam, so that&amp;rsquo;s cool too.
My preparation for BUP:
Beef House burger loaded with mushroom and BBQ sauce from Burger Express, worked out pretty well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RidSCAR</title>
      <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/rrr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 22:14:13 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/rrr/</guid>
      <description>Edit: 29/01/2024; 12:23:20AM
People don&amp;rsquo;t value admiration, really. They value it when they are in danger, they value it when they know that they can&amp;rsquo;t replace you. I am in a journey of changing the tech industry of Bangladesh and sadly in this journey, I leaked some of my emotions to a ruthless person(questionable maybe), who doesn&amp;rsquo;t even value if I die? Seriously? Damn that hurts.
Listen well brothers, never run for girls, NEVER.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RidExpectationSucks</title>
      <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/expectation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 11:47:20 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/expectation/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I was eating snacks along with my family, it was raining outside the weather was chill. Suddenly my Queen told me that &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s a very lucky thing to experience the income of the son. You will buy me a mansion, take me to the Switzerland, buy me a Botique shop at Bailey Road&amp;rdquo;
At first I was enjoying the conversation, it&amp;rsquo;s good to know what your mother needs from you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Rid and why it exists?</title>
      <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fahimfuad.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Heye it&amp;rsquo;s me Fahim Fuad. You know me, else you wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be here. Everyday I wake up, do what I can and capable to do, watch Facebook reels(Okay it is a joke, 99% of the time I never watch reels alone, short videos destroys your focus, useless dopamin leaks) and write shits here, sleep and repeat.
Jokes apart, I am a game engine and graphics programmer from Bangladesh, I ace in Vulkan, OpenGL, DirectX11 rendering APIs, in physics engines I&amp;rsquo;ve used PhysX by NVIDIA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RidMem</title>
      <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/pensieve/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fahimfuad.github.io/pensieve/</guid>
      <description>I dump memories here, jokes, scars, anything I find unique
MemCount: 04
Differentiation-Integration(DI) method aka Table method, pretty cool - Ridhwan
Some people can work upto 18hrs a day, you call them জানোয়ার - Ridhwan
A very Tragic Moment, motivation in one hand, annihilation on the other. - Ridhwan
Medical এ পায়া গেলে upset - Ridhwan</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
