<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ridhwan on RidLines</title>
    <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/authors/ridhwan/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ridhwan on RidLines</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 17:03:49 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fahimfuad.github.io/authors/ridhwan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Donating something actually feels Nice</title>
      <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/donatingisfun/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 17:03:49 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/donatingisfun/</guid>
      <description>Today is my King&amp;rsquo;s birthday, yeah yesterday was my Queen&amp;rsquo;s, not that queen, it&amp;rsquo;s my mother, you idiot. I was outside for some grinding. I was about to buy some stuff then I saw that I had extra 200 taka on my pocket, I donno maybe I forgot to take it out from my pocket last time I wore this pant, typical me. Then I suddenly saw a beggar(kid), looking at the stuff I bought.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Queen&#39;s Birthday &amp; Life~</title>
      <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/queenbirthdayandrecentlife/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 23:04:48 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/queenbirthdayandrecentlife/</guid>
      <description>I am making a new category called &amp;lsquo;Life&amp;rsquo; to post my documentation/memory shits. Some of the previous posts are moved into this category. So today was my mother&amp;rsquo;s birthday. It feels bad as I am running out of time slowly. Her higher secondary level&amp;rsquo;s friend came over today with a surprise cake. I was not expecting that from her friend, but it was nice. I gave away my concept books to Her friends kid as I have the real ones now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hot Reloading C&#43;&#43; Scripts(Part-01)</title>
      <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/hotreloadingcppscripts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 12:41:43 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/hotreloadingcppscripts/</guid>
      <description>In previous post I discussed about the pointers in C++ which is pretty cringe and noob topic. So I will be like normal Ridhwan and jump from noob topic to a highly advanced topic which is used in the game engines like Unreal Engine, C++ hot reloading!
Unlike &amp;lsquo;C#&amp;rsquo;, &amp;rsquo;lua&amp;rsquo; C++ is not often used as a scripting language. Unreal Engine does that somehow &amp;amp; I have no idea how they do that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expectation Sucks</title>
      <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/expectation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 11:47:20 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/expectation/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I was eating snacks along with my family, it was raining outside the weather was chill. Suddenly my Queen told me that &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s a very lucky thing to experience the income of the son. You will buy me a mansion, take me to the Switzerland, buy me a Botique shop at Bailey Road&amp;rdquo;
At first I was enjoying the conversation, it&amp;rsquo;s good to know what your mother needs from you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maybe it will be &#39;worth it&#39; afterall</title>
      <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/matchupbuet/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 15:56:59 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/matchupbuet/</guid>
      <description>I used to follow(still follow) 2 seniors from HSC&#39;22 batch (I was enrolled in ACS Engg&#39;22), I won&amp;rsquo;t expose their names here ofcourse. One of the senior(male) got into BUET in under 300 rank, studying with my dream subject CSE. I was happy for that brother. The other senior(female) also got chance in BUET in Architecture department.
As I follow both of them in Facebook, their update comes in my feed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pointers in C/C&#43;&#43;</title>
      <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/pointersincpp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 12:20:22 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/pointersincpp/</guid>
      <description>Pointers in C/C++Link to headingBefore starting I wanna clarify that, I always wanted to share my knowledge of C++, there are some things in C++ that beginners find hard to catch as it is different from other languages. C++ is a VERY powerful, the fastest programming language to ever exist till now. (To a lot of people it is the hardest language to learn due to it&amp;rsquo;s complexity).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MovieReview002 - The Perks of Being a Wallflower</title>
      <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/moviereviewperksofbeingawallflower/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 00:15:29 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/moviereviewperksofbeingawallflower/</guid>
      <description>The Perks of Being a Wallflower (Drama/Romance) 8/10Link to headingYou can call this movie a &amp;ldquo;GoodWatch~ish&amp;rdquo;.
Firstly, I don&amp;rsquo;t watch romance genre, but some quotes from these movie attaracted me, and say what- It was worth it
This movie is based on a high school dickhead idiot falling in love with his senior (Pretty cringe, but I will allow it because Emma Watson was there). There is a song &amp;ldquo;Could it be another change&amp;rdquo; that I absolutely loved!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MovieReview001 - Uncharted</title>
      <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/moviereviewuncharted/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 22:11:26 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/moviereviewuncharted/</guid>
      <description>Uncharted (Adventure/Action): 6.5/10Link to headingYou can proudly call this movie a quater-shit.
So watched this movie last night, not a big fan of Adventure/Action genre but this movie was good enough. Basically my friend who is unfortunately taller than Tom Holland hit me up to watch this movie.
I liked the minor details in this movie which you can completely miss if you don&amp;rsquo;t watch carefully. Other than that the ending was not upto the mark, I thought of some sorta ending relationship between the Gold Seekers, that would&amp;rsquo;ve been fun to watch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Last Run</title>
      <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/admissionjourneystarts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 13:59:45 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/admissionjourneystarts/</guid>
      <description>So, I finally completed my HSC, hopefully I will pass a with a good marks with my friends. I always thought that finishing HSC will be a blast and enjoyable, but everything feels so vague. ACS classes are long &amp;amp; tiresome to do, but I got no other option at this moment.
The last time I felt these vagueness and identity crisis was not good. I was rejected, rejected from my dream college while my friends got accepted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Message For Future, For Someone</title>
      <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/messageforfutureforsomeone/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 13:36:04 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/messageforfutureforsomeone/</guid>
      <description>Encrypted message for someone which might go live after few months
The Message
Don&amp;rsquo;t click the link, it&amp;rsquo;s not for you. Why post it here? I got reasons. Now Shoo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My first POST!</title>
      <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/firstpost/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 22:28:05 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/firstpost/</guid>
      <description>So you clicked in the link huh? Curious? I got nothing at this moment. Here is a JOKE for you</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
