<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Admission on RidLines</title>
    <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/tags/admission/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Admission on RidLines</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 23:06:03 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fahimfuad.github.io/tags/admission/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My Engineering Entrance Notes</title>
      <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/ridenggnotesallpdf_public/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 23:06:03 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/ridenggnotesallpdf_public/</guid>
      <description>Hey little brain &amp;amp; little IQ(probably negative IQ) entity Here I will list all the Notes of my Engineering Entrance Preparation. Links will be updated chapterwise. Why I am making all these public? Well there are two reasons, one is I want to keep an online PDF in case I lose my orginal copy, and second one is &amp;ldquo;If you love something, set it free&amp;rdquo;. Oh shit কবি হয়ে গেলাম। Anyways, here are the notes, enjoy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expectation Sucks</title>
      <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/expectation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 11:47:20 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/expectation/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I was eating snacks along with my family, it was raining outside the weather was chill. Suddenly my Queen told me that &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s a very lucky thing to experience the income of the son. You will buy me a mansion, take me to the Switzerland, buy me a Botique shop at Bailey Road&amp;rdquo;
At first I was enjoying the conversation, it&amp;rsquo;s good to know what your mother needs from you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Last Run</title>
      <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/admissionjourneystarts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 13:59:45 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/admissionjourneystarts/</guid>
      <description>So, I finally completed my HSC, hopefully I will pass a with a good marks with my friends. I always thought that finishing HSC will be a blast and enjoyable, but everything feels so vague. ACS classes are long &amp;amp; tiresome to do, but I got no other option at this moment.
The last time I felt these vagueness and identity crisis was not good. I was rejected, rejected from my dream college while my friends got accepted.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
