<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on RidLines</title>
    <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on RidLines</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 01:41:33 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>BUP Fail</title>
      <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/bupfail/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 01:41:33 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/bupfail/</guid>
      <description>Meh, I expected on waiting list. Am I expecting too much? I mean I studied nothing for BUP, I shouldn&amp;rsquo;t expect a merit. Funny how the 20K fighting for 250 seats, all of my idiot elite homies are rejected too 😂
Bro who is BUP selecting then? Quota idiots? 😂
I know I shouldn&amp;rsquo;t care about BUP, we don&amp;rsquo;t care for BUP, it was more like a tourist exam&amp;hellip;. but it feels sad for some reason even though I didn&amp;rsquo;t prepare for it, getting rejected is tough.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Site Update x01</title>
      <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/updatex01/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 17:03:47 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/updatex01/</guid>
      <description>Making this site after dumping all my socials is getting addictive xD
UpdatesLink to headingMade a ton of speed improvements Images now loads 2x faster, saved with better compression Hidden Memories section are moved into public RidDiary section. Deleted hidden memories Quality of life updates Fixed broken dark mode light mode switch Made with 💙 by ridhwan.dll</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream A</title>
      <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/scholarship/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 17:09:10 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/scholarship/</guid>
      <description>Got a dream down today, finally. I lowkey expected talentpool, which started from 1190(approximately), I got 1184 :)
But hey, 048th in general is not bad, 1st from Joseph EV ✌️, 3rd from Whole Joseph
AND
162th in Dhaka Board!
Man it feels so good to fulfill promises, I promised my queen of this, made it and she was like &amp;ldquo;পাইস তাইলে, ভালোই&amp;rdquo;, this is not a complement, got none but hey, I know She is really happy inside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BUP Drill</title>
      <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/bupdrill/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 00:10:50 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/bupdrill/</guid>
      <description>BUP was a nice experience, cantonment is nice, the environment was nice. Question standard was pretty okay even though I was not able to unleash my full potential there, 250 seats for 20K in FST, pretty hard. My brain was vibing on One Kiss by Dua Lipa during the exam, so that&amp;rsquo;s cool too.
My preparation for BUP:
Beef House burger loaded with mushroom and BBQ sauce from Burger Express, worked out pretty well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rid is Rid of Rid</title>
      <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/rrr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 22:14:13 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/rrr/</guid>
      <description>People don&amp;rsquo;t value love, really. They value it when they are in danger, they value it when they know that they can&amp;rsquo;t replace me. The days when I will become the richest man on my blood-line are hopefully near, I mean I already started a company which is undercover, I am in dreams of changing this country&amp;rsquo;s tech industry, sadly in this journey, I leaked some of my emotions to a ruthless person(questionable), who doesn&amp;rsquo;t even value if I die?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Engineering Entrance Notes</title>
      <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/ridenggnotesallpdf_public/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 23:06:03 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/ridenggnotesallpdf_public/</guid>
      <description>Physics 1st PaperLink to headingVector: NOTE Newtonian Mechanics(Linear): NOTE Newtonian Mechanics(Angular): NOTE Work, Power &amp;amp; Energy: Gravity &amp;amp; Gravitation: Structural Properties of Matter: Periodic Motion: Ideal Gas: Physics 2nd PaperLink to headingThermodynamics: Static Electricity: Current Electricity: Physical Optics: Nuclear Physics: Modern Physics: Semiconductor &amp;amp; Electronics: Chemistry 1st PaperLink to headingQualitative Chemistry: Periodic Properties of Elements and Chemical Bond Chemical Changes(Kp Kc): Vinegar: Chemistry 2nd PaperLink to headingEnvironmental Chemistry: ORGANIC CHEMISTRY: Stoichiometric Chemistry: Electro Chemistry: Higher Mathematics 1st PaperLink to headingMatrix &amp;amp; Determinant: Straight Lines: NOTE Circle: Trigonometry: Differentiation: Integration: Higher Mathematics 2nd PaperLink to headingComplex Numbers: Polynomial &amp;amp; Polynomial Equation: Conics: Inverse Trigonometry: Statics(💀): Dynamics(💀): </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hot Reloading C&#43;&#43; Scripts(Part-01)</title>
      <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/hotreloadingcppscripts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 12:41:43 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/hotreloadingcppscripts/</guid>
      <description>In previous post I discussed about the pointers in C++ which is pretty cringe and noob topic. So I will be like normal Ridhwan and jump from noob topic to a highly advanced topic which is used in the game engines like Unreal Engine, C++ hot reloading!
Unlike &amp;lsquo;C#&amp;rsquo;, &amp;rsquo;lua&amp;rsquo; C++ is not often used as a scripting language. Unreal Engine does that somehow &amp;amp; I have no idea how they do that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expectation Sucks</title>
      <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/expectation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 11:47:20 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/expectation/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I was eating snacks along with my family, it was raining outside the weather was chill. Suddenly my Queen told me that &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s a very lucky thing to experience the income of the son. You will buy me a mansion, take me to the Switzerland, buy me a Botique shop at Bailey Road&amp;rdquo;
At first I was enjoying the conversation, it&amp;rsquo;s good to know what your mother needs from you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pointers in C/C&#43;&#43;</title>
      <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/pointersincpp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 12:20:22 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/pointersincpp/</guid>
      <description>Pointers in C/C++Link to headingBefore starting I wanna clarify that, I always wanted to share my knowledge of C++, there are some things in C++ that beginners find hard to catch as it is different from other languages. C++ is a VERY powerful, the fastest programming language to ever exist till now. (To a lot of people it is the hardest language to learn due to it&amp;rsquo;s complexity).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MovieReview002 - The Perks of Being a Wallflower</title>
      <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/moviereviewperksofbeingawallflower/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 00:15:29 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/moviereviewperksofbeingawallflower/</guid>
      <description>The Perks of Being a Wallflower (Drama/Romance) 8/10Link to headingYou can call this movie a &amp;ldquo;GoodWatch~ish&amp;rdquo;.
Firstly, I don&amp;rsquo;t watch romance genre, but some quotes from these movie attaracted me, and say what- It was worth it
This movie is based on a high school dickhead idiot falling in love with his senior (Pretty cringe, but I will allow it because Emma Watson was there). There is a song &amp;ldquo;Could it be another change&amp;rdquo; that I absolutely loved!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MovieReview001 - Uncharted</title>
      <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/moviereviewuncharted/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 22:11:26 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/moviereviewuncharted/</guid>
      <description>Uncharted (Adventure/Action): 6.5/10Link to headingYou can proudly call this movie a quater-shit.
So watched this movie last night, not a big fan of Adventure/Action genre but this movie was good enough. Basically my friend who is unfortunately taller than Tom Holland hit me up to watch this movie.
I liked the minor details in this movie which you can completely miss if you don&amp;rsquo;t watch carefully. Other than that the ending was not upto the mark, I thought of some sorta ending relationship between the Gold Seekers, that would&amp;rsquo;ve been fun to watch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Last Run</title>
      <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/admissionjourneystarts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 13:59:45 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/admissionjourneystarts/</guid>
      <description>So, I finally completed my HSC, hopefully I will pass a with a good marks with my friends. I always thought that finishing HSC will be a blast and enjoyable, but everything feels so vague. ACS classes are long &amp;amp; tiresome to do, but I got no other option at this moment.
The last time I felt these vagueness and identity crisis was not good. I was rejected, rejected from my dream college while my friends got accepted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My first POST!</title>
      <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/firstpost/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 22:28:05 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/firstpost/</guid>
      <description>So you clicked in the link huh? Curious? I got nothing at this moment. Here is a JOKE for you</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
