<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Life on RidLines</title>
    <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/categories/life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Life on RidLines</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 17:03:49 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fahimfuad.github.io/categories/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Donating something actually feels Nice</title>
      <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/donatingisfun/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 17:03:49 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/donatingisfun/</guid>
      <description>Today is my King&amp;rsquo;s birthday, yeah yesterday was my Queen&amp;rsquo;s, not that queen, it&amp;rsquo;s my mother, you idiot. I was outside for some grinding. I was about to buy some stuff then I saw that I had extra 200 taka on my pocket, I donno maybe I forgot to take it out from my pocket last time I wore this pant, typical me. Then I suddenly saw a beggar(kid), looking at the stuff I bought.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Queen&#39;s Birthday &amp; Life~</title>
      <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/queenbirthdayandrecentlife/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 23:04:48 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/queenbirthdayandrecentlife/</guid>
      <description>I am making a new category called &amp;lsquo;Life&amp;rsquo; to post my documentation/memory shits. Some of the previous posts are moved into this category. So today was my mother&amp;rsquo;s birthday. It feels bad as I am running out of time slowly. Her higher secondary level&amp;rsquo;s friend came over today with a surprise cake. I was not expecting that from her friend, but it was nice. I gave away my concept books to Her friends kid as I have the real ones now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Last Run</title>
      <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/admissionjourneystarts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 13:59:45 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/admissionjourneystarts/</guid>
      <description>So, I finally completed my HSC, hopefully I will pass a with a good marks with my friends. I always thought that finishing HSC will be a blast and enjoyable, but everything feels so vague. ACS classes are long &amp;amp; tiresome to do, but I got no other option at this moment.
The last time I felt these vagueness and identity crisis was not good. I was rejected, rejected from my dream college while my friends got accepted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Message For Future, For Someone</title>
      <link>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/messageforfutureforsomeone/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 13:36:04 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fahimfuad.github.io/posts/messageforfutureforsomeone/</guid>
      <description>Encrypted message for someone which might go live after few months
The Message
Don&amp;rsquo;t click the link, it&amp;rsquo;s not for you. Why post it here? I got reasons. Now Shoo.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
